

HUNG BUI TUAN

WEB DEVELOPER

With over a year experience in website programming, my primary goal is to become a full-time Full-stack developer. I have a good base knowledge in web development and have applied this knowledge in projects which have practical applicability.

CONTACT

- 0392949429

- District 7, Ho Chi Minh City
- شم 2001

EDUCATION

Post and telecommunications institute of technology

Major: Software Engineering - GPA 3.0

Awarded scholarships in the second semester of the third year and the first semester of the fourth year at the school.

SKILLS

FRONT-END

- HTML/CSS (SASS)
- Javascript (ES6+) / Typescript
- Boostrap 5, TailwindCSS
- · AntDesign, Mantine UI
- · Redux, ReactJs, NextJs

BACK-END

- · Java, NodeJs
- ExpressJs, NestJs
- · Restful Api, GraphQL
- MySQL, MSSQL, MongoDB
- · Docker, AWS

OTHER SKILLS

- Git/Github, Visual Studio
- · Understood software development methodologies
- Capable of reading/writing documents in English.
- · Have a good teamwork spirit and desire to learn, friendly and team player

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVERLOPER INTERN, FPT IS BUILDING CMS SYSTEM

(05/2023 - 08/2023)

Overview	Develop a multi-user CMS system.
Technologies	Front-end: ReactJs, NextJs 12, MantineUI, Vercel SWR, Bootstrap 5, Back-end: NestJs, JWT, Prisma ORM, MySql
Feature	ISR: Incremental Server-side Rendering Search, view, and interact with articles Manage articles, draft articles, submit for approval, approve articles, request articles Manage users: assign roles Manage website configurations.
Demo	Client: https://hocvankhongvatva.vercel.app Admin: https://hocvankhongvatva.vercel.app/admin
Source	https://github.com/SourceControls/BlogHocVanKhongVatVa

YOUTUBE MUSIC PLAYER

(01/2023 - 02/2023)

Overview	A personal music app that allows creating playlists from YouTube URLs.
Technologies	HTML / CSS / Javascript NodeJs / ExpressJs Firebase
Demo	https://youtube-music-player.hung-public.lol/
Source	https://github.com/SourceControls/YoutubeMusicPlayer

Overview	Design and build a landing page introducing the PlayStation 5 product.
Technologies	HTML / CSS (SASS) / Javascript
Demo	https://sourcecontrols.github.io/PLaystation5/
Source	https://github.com/SourceControls/PLaystation5

OTHER PROJECTS

Watch Store (8/2022 - 9/2022)	Overview: Build a multi-language online watch-selling system for the store using the SSR (Server-Side Rendering) mechanism. Technologies: Java Spring Boot, Hibernate. Members: 2. Role: Full-stack developer. Source: https://github.com/SourceControls/CampusProjects/tree/main/WatchStore-v2
Manage GymGuest (11/2022 - 12/2022)	Overview: Develop a system to manage gym customers, including the registration for service usage and customer payment management and develop AI recommendation feature. Technologies: JavaScript, bootstrap, nodeJs, SQL Server, Python Members: 3. Role: Front-end developer, recommendation feature developer Source: https://github.com/SourceControls/CampusProjects/tree/main/Manage GymGuests-v2
Tour Booking (03/2023 - 05/2023)	Overview: Develop a system for managing and booking travel tours. Technologies: ReactJs, NodeJs, MySQL. Members: 4. Role: Full-stack Web developer. Source: https://github.com/SourceControls/CampusProjects/tree/main/TourBooking

OTHER PROJECTS

Management

(05/2023 -

07/2023)

Overview: Develop a system for managing a fried chicken store and

counter orders.

Lotte Technologies: ReactJs, MantineUI, Axios, NodeJs, MySQL.

Members: 5.

Role: Front-end developer, API designer.

Source:

https://github.com/SourceControls/CampusProjects/tree/main/LotteriaM

<u>anagement</u>

CERTIFICATE

JavaScript Algorithms & Data Structures

Organization: FreeCodeCamp - July 2022

Note: Completed the JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures certification from

FreeCodeCamp. After the course, I am capable of solving complex algorithms and working with data structures using the JavaScript language.

Responsive Web Design

Organization: FreeCodeCamp - August 2022

Note: Earned the Responsive Web Design certification from FreeCodeCamp.

After the course, I have the ability to create web designs optimized for various

devices and screen sizes.

OTHER ACTIVITIES

Member of the Connectivity Club (2021).

Responsibility: Design banners and videos for the club's communication activities and events

Club fanpage: https://www.facebook.com/ketnoiclub

Volunteer for the 'Mid-Autumn Festival for Children' program (09/2023).

Responsibility: Fundraising through sales for the program, organizing games for the children

Program details: https://fb.watch/mhuTeajht9/

• Full-time server at a cafe (06/2017 - 07/2017).